{"questions":[{"question":"In black box testing we _____ .","level":"1","answers":["know the software and test the actual code.","know the software and test functionality.","don't know the software and test actual code.","don't know the software and test functionality."],"team":"Piranha","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"Program testing is _____ .","level":"2","answers":["an effeictive way to show absence of bugs.","is not effective to show presence of bugs.","can't assure absence of bugs.","none of the above."],"team":"Piranha","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"What is a legacy system ?","level":"2","answers":["Big systems with so many developers maintain it daily.","older systems that rely on languages and technology that are no longer used for new systems development.","small systems like the one we are working on in the course.","bank systems."],"team":"Piranha","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"What is the type that is non relevant to maintaince from the given answers?","level":"2","answers":["corrective maintenance.","adaptive maintenance.","logical maintenance.","perfective maintenance."],"team":"Piranha","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"The part in the lifecycle of a system that needs most effort and most costly financialy is ?","level":"2","answers":["Implementation.","Maintanance.","Requirment Collecting.","Designing."],"team":"Piranha","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"What is Agile?","level":"1","answers":["Iterative approach to project management.","Breakdown of project activities into linear sequential phases.","Each phase depends on the deliverables of the previous one and corresponds to a specialisation of tasks.","none of the above."],"team":"Piranha","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"What is “Principal” ?","level":"3","answers":["Implies a degree of importance that grants a design decision.","a set of architectural design decisions that are applicable to a recurring design problem.","is the process of determining a software system’s architecture from its implementation-level artifacts.","an approach to software development where models rather than programs."],"team":"Piranha","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"What is “Principal” ?","level":"3","answers":["Implies a degree of importance that grants a design decision.","a set of architectural design decisions that are applicable to a recurring design problem.","is the process of determining a software system’s architecture from its implementation-level artifacts.","an approach to software development where models rather than programs."],"team":"Piranha","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"What is the pros of Usage of model-driven engineering?","level":"3","answers":["Models for abstraction and not necessarily right for implementation.","Savings from generating code may be outweighed by the costs of developing translators for new platforms.","Allows systems to be considered at higher levels of abstraction & Generating code automatically means that it is cheaper to adapt systems to new platforms.","There is no pros in usage of model-driven engineering."],"team":"Piranha","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"What is the attribute that is not relevant to Waterfall from the given answers?","level":"2","answers":["Poor quality.","Poor visibility.","Testing starts from day one.","Too risky."],"team":"Piranha","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Whats the first step we should do before we start our project?","level":"1","answers":["Requirements.","Development plan.","Contract review.","Quality plan."],"team":"Piranha","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"What is Verifiability in Review checks?","level":"3","answers":["Is the requirement properly understood?","Is the origin of the requirement clearly stated?","Can the requirement be changed without a large impact on other requirements?","Is the requirement realistically testable?"],"team":"Piranha","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"Choose the wrong answer - Why Legacy systems are expensive to change?","level":"3","answers":["Consistent programming style.","System structure degradation.","Program optimizations may make them hard to understand.","Data errors, duplication and inconsistency."],"team":"Piranha","correct_ans":"1"}]}